Inter-University Case Program Records
Inter-University Case Program Records
1948-2015
Bock, Edwin A.
12 linear ft.
Case studies, books, and other published items; editorial drafts and related correspondence and research material; board meeting minutes and planning documents; and administrative files and correspondence.
2458929
Biographical History
The Inter-University Case Program (ICP) funded and published case studies of government decision-making as well as related materials for teaching of Public Administration and Political Science. (In its first three years, the organization was known as the Committee on Public Administration Cases or CPAC.)
Between 1948 and 1991, the ICP published 164 case studies and special studies of government decision-making and administration for departments of Political Science and Public Administration in over 60 member universities. Most of the studies dealt with American government, but some, mostly after 1960, described situations in Britain, Europe, and developing countries in Asia. This collection includes all ICP publications as well as "case method" publications that deal with case preparation, case teaching, and the relation of case studies to academic theorizing in Political Science and Public Administration. The collection also includes minutes of the ICP Board meetings at which case projects were planned and drafts of cases critically reviewed.
Beginning in 1958 the ICP, with support from the Ford Foundation, encouraged the use of the case method in related fields (e.g., social welfare and public health administration) and by interested universities and government training institutions in Europe and Asia. Studies, correspondence, and memoranda about these efforts are included in this collection.
The ICP Board included a number of eminent scholars who were part of the movement, begun in the 1930s, to make more realistic (and less solely legalistic) university teaching and theorizing about the workings of government in America. (Syracuse University's Special Collections Research Center also has a number of other collections related to this topic; see Related Material.) Correspondence with these Board members is included in this collection, as are the case preparation file folders for most of the published and quite a number of unpublished cases; some of these contain interesting correspondence about factual matters from public officials described in the cases.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Inter-University Case Program Records consists of case studies, books, and other published items; editorial drafts and related correspondence and research material; board meeting minutes and planning documents; and administrative files and correspondence.
Separated Material
Published case studies have been transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to and search for the phrase "inter-university case program" as a keyword.
Related Material
See also the
Alan K. Campbell Papers
and
Donald Stone Papers
.
Subject and Genre Headings
Politics, government and public administration; Business and Industry; Appleby, Paul.; Bock, Edwin A.; Campbell, Alan K.; Stone, Donald Crawford, 1903-; Inter-university Case Program.; American Society for Public Administration.; Committee on Public Administration Cases.; CASE method.; Federal government -- United States.; Intergovernmental cooperation.; Inter-university Case Program.; CPAC case studies.; Municipal government -- United States.; Public administration -- Case studies.; Public administration -- India.; Public administration -- Ireland.; Public administration -- United States.; Bank statements.; Case studies.; Correspondence.; Essays.; Meeting minutes.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Edwin Bock, 2004-2005
Inventory
- Introductory material
  - The ICP: A Twenty-Five Year History, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Guide to the 1948-1990 Archive of the Inter-University Case Program, by Edwin Bock, 2015 (Box 1)
    This document is also available online via SURFACE.
- Case studies published by CPAC/ICP
  Published material has been transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please refer to and search for the phrase "inter-university case program" as a keyword.
  Published material includes the following types of material. Of special interest to researchers will be the indexes to cases, as these categorize the cases under a variety of topics and headings.
  Cases published by CPAC/ICP (shelved in Rare Books)
  Indexes to cases (shelved in Rare Books)
  Hardcover texts (shelved in Rare Books)
  Special studies undertaken by Case Program (shelved in Rare Books)
  Research reports partly funded by Case Program (shelved in Rare Books)
  - List of published CPAC and ICP cases (Box 1)
- Case method material
  - Case method theory and practice
    - Case writing and editing guides (Box 1)
    - Essays, booklets and pamphlets
      - Preparation of Case Studies: The Problem of Abundance (Harold Stein), 1951 (Box 1)
      - Using Public Administration Cases (E.A. Bock), 1957 (Box 1)
      - Essays on the Case Method (E.A. Bock, James Fesler, Harold Stein, Dwight Waldo), 1962; Published as ICP 109 - cataloged and shelved in Rare Books
      - The Editing of ICP Case Studies: Some Helps to Authors, 1967 (Box 1)
      - Improving the Usefulness of the Case Study in Political Science (E.A. Bock), 1970; Cataloged and shelved in Rare Books
      - The Syracuse Total Policy Exercise: Overcoming Some of the Limitations of Decision-Forcing Cases (E.A. Bock), 1980; Published as ICP 130 - cataloged and shelved in Rare Books
    - Theoretical Aspects of CPAC and ICP cases, 1949-1961 (James Heaphey), Dissertation (Box 1)
    - Reviews of ICP cases and case books (Box 1)
    - Experimental project of developing case materials for high school teaching, by Mary Iversen, Feb 1965 (Box 1)
  - Other U.S. case programs
    - Harvard JFK School cases, 1991 (Box 1)
    - University of Washington Electronic Hallway, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Finished but unpublished CPAC/ICP cases (by date)
    - Treasury vs the Federal Reserve (James Fesler), 1958 (Box 1)
    - The Government Center of Boston (Richard W. Nathan), 1960 (Box 1)
    - A Budget Law for Venezuela (Sidney Baldwin), 1961 (Box 1)
    - List of cases published and in progress as of 1961, 1961 (Box 1)
    - Eden Reforms of the British Foreign Service (Paul Ylvisaker), 1963 (Box 1)
    - A Revolt in the Provinces (Kenneth Tollenaar), 1967 (Box 2)
  - Foreign cases
    - Assisted by ICP
      - Location of the Brick and Tile Factory at Skopje (Aleksandr Hristov and Angel Klisinski), 1961 (Box 2)
      - The B.E.S.T. Strike (D'Souza, Bombay), 1967 (Box 2)
      - The Rate of Return (K.N. Butani, New Delhi), 1968 (Box 2)
      - Transfer of the Collector of Matsya Pura (ICP), 1969 (Box 2)
      - Starting the Punjab Tractor Finance Project (Tejendra Khanna), 1973 (Box 2)
    - Independent Indian cases
      - Special Areas Development Program in the Andamans (K.N. Butani, India Institute of Public Administration), 1968 (Box 2)
      - When the Trust Was Betrayed (N.K. Sethi, Jaipur), 1973 (Box 2)
      - Case Studies in Rural Banking (B.Y. Raju, Hyderabad), 1987 (Box 2)
      - Case Study Program and Award Competition Scheme, New (DelhiIndian Institute of Public Administration), 1990; Back page lists all public administration cases published by case study unit of the Indian Institute of Public Administration (Box 2)
      - Cases from Case Study Project (Rajasthan State Institute of Public Administration), 1991 (Box 2)
      - Cases in Administration (National Academy of Public Administration, Mussoorie), 1991 (Box 2)
  - Case preparation and editing files (alpha by author)
    - Bock, E.A. and Gorvine, A. - Scientific Panel in Foreign Affairs: The Revelle Report (Box 2)
    - Bock, E.A. and Gorvine, A. - Scientific Panel in Foreign Affairs: The Revelle Report (cont.) (Box 3)
    - Campbell, Warren - Berkeley Master Plan, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Campbell, Warren - Improvement of N. Shattuck Ave, Berkeley (Box 3)
    - Chapman, Richard - Tiros-Nimbus Weather Satellite, includes photos; 4 folders (Box 3)
    - Edgerton, Russell - Forming the Development Loan Fund, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Ershkowitz, Miriam - Dept. of Air Pollution Control, NYC (Box 4)
    - Fainstein, Susan - Lead Poisoning, Staff Dismissal (Box 4)
    - Feldstein, Sylvan - Brownsville School Problems, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Flash, Edward S. - Battle of Cow Green (Box 5)
    - Frischknecht, R. - Meat Packer Legislation in the 84th Congress, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Galloway, John - The Gulf of Tonkin Resolution (Box 5)
    - Gold, Robert L. - Smith and the OPA (Box 5)
    - Goldsmith, William - Growth of a Non-Profit Housing Corporation (Box 5)
    - Goodall, Merrill - Struggle for Planned Growth in Claremont, CA (Box 5)
    - Greenblatt, Michael - The Welfare Office – Notes from Underground (Box 5)
    - Gremion, Catherine - Les Réformes Administratives Départementales de Régionales de Mars 1964, 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Gremion, Catherine - Décision ou Indécision Dans la Haute Administration Française, 5 folders (Box 6)
    - Hahn, Walter - Weather Bureau Regionalization (Box 6)
    - Henry, Laurin - NASA-Universities Memorandum of Understanding, 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Hipple, Byron - NY State Implements Changes in Grant-in-Aid Program, 4 folders (Box 7)
    - Hogarty, Richard - Delaware River Drought Emergency (Box 7)
    - Huitt, Ralph - Lyndon Johnson as Majority Leader (Box 7)
    - Johnannes, Jack - Los Angeles Coroner (Box 7)
    - Khanna, Tejendra - Punjab Tractor Project (Box 7)
    - Kvam, Roger A. and Lambright, W. Henry - The Invention of ComSat, Jan 1968; typed draft, 119 pp.; handwritten notation reads "ICP #203" (Box 24)
    - Lambright, W. Henry - Weather Modification: The Politics of an Emergent Technology, photocopy, 506 pp.; handwritten notation reads "ICP #215"; 3 folders (Box 24)
    - Reed, Alan - Los Alamos, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Reed, Alan - Los Alamos (cont.), 3 folders (Box 8)
    - Simon, James F. - Planning Problems in an Indian District: An Eyewitness View, typed draft, 59pp.; handwritten notation reads "ICP #205" (Box 24)
    - Various - Irish Fluoridation, 7 folders; trial notes and analysis, interviews, newspaper clippings, documents relating to U.S. participation in trial (Box 8)
    - Various - Irish Fluoridation (cont.), 5 folders; trial notes and analysis, interviews, newspaper clippings, documents relating to U.S. participation in trial (Box 9)
    - Various - Scottish Fluoridation, 1 folder (Box 9)
    - Various - Photographs related to various cases (Box 9)
- Corporation and Board of Trustees material
  - Meeting minutes and related material
    - Meetings, 1948; verbatim notes, final published minutes; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Meetings, 1949; verbatim notes, final published minutes, CPAC 1st Annual Report; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Meetings, 1950; verbatim notes, final published minutes, CPAC 2d Annual Report (Box 9)
    - Meetings, 1950 (cont.); verbatim notes, final published minutes, CPAC 2d Annual Report (Box 10)
    - Meetings, 1951; verbatim notes, final published minutes, Executive Board Meeting #1, 2, 3; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Meetings, 1952; verbatim notes, National Committee Meeting, final minutes, Executive Board Meeting #4, 5, 6; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Meetings, 1953; verbatim notes, final minutes, Executive Board Meeting #7, 8, 9, material sent to Board members; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Meetings, 1954; verbatim notes, final minutes, Executive Board Meeting #10, 11, 12, 13, material sent to Board members; 4 folders (Box 10)
    - Meetings, 1954 (cont.); verbatim notes, final minutes, Executive Board Meeting #10, 11, 12, 13, material sent to Board members; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Meetings, 1955; verbatim notes, final minutes, Executive Board Meeting #14, 15, 16, material sent to Board members; 5 folders (Box 11)
    - Meetings, 1956, Jan-May; verbatim notes, final minutes, Executive Board Meeting #17, 18, 19, 20, material sent to Board members; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Meetings, 1956, Jun-Dec; verbatim notes, final minutes, Executive Board Meeting #17, 18, 19, 20, material sent to Board members (Box 12)
    - Meetings, 1957; Executive Board Meeting #22 minutes, material sent to Board members, including Executive Board Meeting #23 (Box 12)
    - Meetings, 1958; Material sent to Board members, including Executive Board Meeting #25 (Box 12)
    - Meetings, 1959; Material sent to Board members, including Executive Board Meeting #26 (Box 12)
    - Meetings, 1960; Material sent to Board members, including Executive Board Meeting #25, ICP Research Committee Meeting #2 (Box 12)
    - Meetings, 1961; Material sent to Board members, including Executive Board Meeting #29, cluster committee budget information (Box 13)
    - Meetings, 1962; Executive Board Meeting #30, 31, 32; misc board correspondence (Box 13)
    - Meetings, 1963; National Committee Meeting; Executive Board Meeting #33; ICP Board of Trustees Meeting minutes #1, 2, 3; Material sent to Board members. Includes material relating to incorporation of ICP.; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Meetings, 1964; Board of Trustees Meeting #4 minutes (Box 13)
    - Meetings, 1965; Board of Trustees Meeting minutes; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Meetings, 1966; Board of Trustees Meeting minutes (Box 13)
    - Meetings, 1966 (cont.); Board of Trustees Meeting minutes; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Meetings, 1967; Board of Trustees Meeting minutes; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Meetings, 1968; Board of Trustees Meeting minutes; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Meetings, 1969; Board of Trustees Meeting minutes (Box 14)
    - Meetings, 1973; Board of Trustees Meeting minutes (Box 14)
    - Lists of members of corporation and Board of Trustees, various years, 1948-1990 (Box 14)
  - Board Members to/from E.A. Bock
    - Miscellaneous board members (Box 14)
    - Appleby, Paul
      Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Bailey, Stephen K. ("Steve") (Box 14)
      Additional material in microfilm index
    - Banfield, Edward, Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Caldwell, Lynton K. ("Keith") (Box 14)
    - Campbell, Alan K. ("Scotty") (Box 14)
    - Carey, William D. ("Bill"), 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Cleaveland, Frederic ("Fred") (Box 15)
    - Cleveland, Harlan, Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Egger, Rowland, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Fainsod, Merle, Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Fenno, Richard F. Jr ("Dick") (Box 15)
    - Fesler, James W. ("Jim"), 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Garceau, Oliver (Box 15)
    - Graham, George A., includes copy of Woodrow Wilson "interview"; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Hammond, Paul Y. (Box 15)
    - Heady, Ferrel (Box 15)
    - Henry, Laurin L. (Box 15)
    - Herring, Pendleton ("Pen") (Box 16)
    - Honey, John C. (Box 16)
    - Kaufman, Herbert ("Herb") (Box 16)
    - Lowi, Theodore ("Ted") (Box 16)
    - Leiserson, Avery, Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Mansfield, Harvey C., includes oral history interview, 2 Dec 1988; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Martin, Roscoe C., Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Masland, John W. (Box 16)
    - Millett, John D., Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Mosher, Frederick C. ("Fritz"), 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P. ("Pat") (Box 16)
    - Neustadt, Richard E. ("Dick") (Box 17)
    - Olson, Emery E., Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Ostrom, Vincent, Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Price, Don K. (Box 17)
    - Redford, Emmette S. (Box 17)
    - Reining, Henry, Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Riggs, Fred, Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Sayre, Wallace S. ("Wally"), 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Sherwood, Frank P. (Box 17)
    - Short, Lloyd M., Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Somers, Herman M. ("Red") (Box 18)
    - Stein, Harold, Memorial Tribute (Box 18)
    - Stene, Edwin O., Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Stone, Donald, Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Truman, David B., Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Waldo, Dwight, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Wengert, E.S., Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - White, Gilbert, Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Willbern, York (Box 18)
    - Wood, Robert C. (Box 18)
    - Ylvisaker, Paul, Microfilm only, see microfilm index
  - Other to/from E.A. Bock, See also microfilm index for additional correspondents not listed here.
    - American Political Science Association (APSA), Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - American Society of Public Administration (ASPA), Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Birkhead, Guthrie (Box 18)
    - Brasz, Hank A. (Box 18)
    - Brookings Institution (Box 18)
    - Carnegie Corporation, Microfilm only, see microfilm index
    - Crozier, Michel (Box 18)
    - Deng, M. Achol (Box 18)
    - Dror, Yehezkel (Box 18)
    - Eklund, H.J. (Box 18)
    - Fill, Gerald (Box 18)
    - Gambaccini, Louis L., Includes testimony before Transportation Subcommittee on energy conservation and mass transit, 10/5/77 (Box 18)
    - Kaplan, Seymour R. (Box 18)
    - National Association of Schools of Public Affairs and Adminstration (NASPAA) (Box 18)
    - National Defense University (Box 18)
    - National War College (Box 18)
    - Prestemon, David (Box 18)
    - Public Administration [PhD.] Exams (Box 19)
    - Reagan, Michael (Box 19)
    - Webb, James, Includes several interview transcripts (Box 19)
    - Misc P-R (Box 19)
    - Misc X-Y-Z (Box 19)
- Publication and copyright material
  - Copyright
    - Copyright applications (Box 19)
    - Copyright renewals (Box 19)
    - Copyright miscellanea (Box 19)
  - Printing/publisher material
    - Permissions, permission to reprint, include in books, etc; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Alabama, University of (Box 20)
    - Bobbs Merrill (Box 20)
    - Harcourt Brace (Box 20)
    - Oxford University Press (Box 20)
    - Prentice Hall, 4 folders (Box 20)
    - Mailing lists (printed labels) (Box 20)
- Miscellaneous
  - Administrative
    - Incorporation material, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Reports to Carnegie Corporation (Box 20)
    - ICP at SU material, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - ICP windup material, 1998-2004 (Box 21)
    - Ford Foundation, 4 folders; Contains correspondence and other material related to 1957 grant proposal for expanded 5-year program, grant proposal for 1962-1967 program, details of Foundation's two terminal grants, and newsletter. (Box 21)
    - Day files, 1981-1985; 5 folders (Box 21)
  - Financial
    - Financial reports, 1953; 1954,; 1955 (Box 21)
    - Bank accounts information, Jul 1956 thru March 1975 (Box 21)
    - Ledger, 1970-1982 (Box 21)
    - Financial commitments to case writers (Box 22)
  - Sales
    - Desk copies information (Box 22)
    - Price Lists (Box 22)
    - Sales reports (Box 22)
- Microfilm
  Snapshot of files of Case Program as of 1963. Ten reels; each reel also has a corresponding negative reel which is not listed here. Of particular interest to researchers: American Political Science Association (APSA); American Society of Public Administration (ASPA); Appleby, Paul; Bailey, Stephen K.; Banfield, Edward; Carnegie Corporation Correspondence (1948-1962; Cleveland, Harlan; Fainsod, Merle; Fesler, James W.; Garceau, Oliver; Graham, George; Herring, Pendleton; Kaufman, Herbert; Martin, Roscoe C.; Millett, John D.; Olson, Emery E.; Ostrom, Vincent; Reining, Henry Jr.; Riggs, Fred; Sherwood, Frank; Short, Lloyd M.; Stene; Edwin O.; Stone, Donald; Truman, David B.; Wengert, E.S.; Ylvisaker, Paul; White, Gilbert.
  - CPAC to SU correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 23, Reel 63-1)
  - IUCP miscellaneous correspondence (A thru O), 1950-1958 (Box 23, Reel 63-1)
  - IUCP miscellaneous correspondence (P thru Z), 1950-1958 (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
  - IUCP general files, 1951-1963 (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
  - Correspondence, alphabetical
    - A, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - University of Alabama Press, 1952-1962; Case Orders and Requests; Case Sales: Office Records; Case Studies, Indexes and Summaries of; Correspondence, 1952-1962; Invoices 1962 (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - American Political Science Association (APSA) (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - American Society of Public Administration (ASPA), Chapel Hill Conference, Sept 1959; Comparative Administration Group (CAG); Correspondence (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - Appleby, Paul (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - Arnow, Kathryn (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - Ascher, Charles (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - B, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - Bailey, Stephen K. (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - Banfield, Edward (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - Beany, William (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - Brookings Institution, Conference, Oct 1960; Laurin Henry, etc (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - C, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-2)
    - Carnegie Corporation correspondence, 1948-1962 (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Carper, Edith (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Carroll, J.J. (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Case Awards, 1952 (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Case Conference, St. Louis, Oct 1952 (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Case distribution and inventory, 1948-1952 (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Case Ideas (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Case possibilities: Dissertations (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Case possibilities: General (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Case programs in related fields (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Cases: Requests to Use (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Cases: Reviews (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Case users surveys, 1960; 1961 (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Case writers, payments to, through 1956 (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Case writing guide (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Charlesworth, James C. (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Chester, Norman (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Civil servants, international (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Cleveland, Harlan (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - CNO cases: Raebeck and NCJW (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Copyright, Register of (originals retained) (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Culbertson, Jack – UCEA (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - E, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Eagleton Foundation (Herzberg and Tillett correspondence) (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Eliot, Thomas H. (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Emmerich, Herbert (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Enarson, Harold (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Executive Board Meeting No. 32 (Box 23, Reel 63-3)
    - Executive Board Meeting No's 31 – 1 (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - F, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Fainsod, Merle (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Fesler, James W. (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Finkle, Jason L. (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Fiser, Webb (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Flom, Floyd (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Foreign Service Institute (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Ford Foundation Grant Application, 1957-1962 (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Foundations, general (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Future [of] program post-1957 (relative to Ford Foundation) (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - G, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Garceau, Oliver (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Graham, George A. (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Gross, Bertram (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - H, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Hammond, Paul Y. (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Harcourt, Brace, Agreements and Contracts; Correspondence; Distribution and Review Letters for Stein Casebook (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Harvey, Lashley (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Herring, Pendleton ("Pen") (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - Herzog, Paul M. (Box 23, Reel 63-4)
    - I, miscellaneous (Box 23, Reel 63-4)